[
    {
        "question": "An isosceles triangle has lengths 8 and 4. Determine all possible values of the length of the last leg.",
        "answer": "c",
        "choices": {
            "a": "4",
            "b": "4,8",
            "c": "8",
            "d": "No possible value satisfies the given conditions."
        }
    },

    {
        "question": " Let <i>Q</i> be a binary operator such that <i>aQb = ab - a - b</i> . Determine <i>4 Q (2 Q 2 )</i>.",
        "answer": "b",
        "choices": {
            "a": "-2",
            "b": "-4",
            "c": "2",
            "d": "4"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Given that 2016 = 2<sup>5</sup> * 3<sup>2</sup> * 7, 49 = 7<sup>2</sup>, and 128 = 2<sup>7</sup>, determine the least common multiple of 2016, 128, and 49",
        "answer": "d",
        "choices": {
            "a": "1",
            "b": "2<sup>12</sup> * 3<sup>2</sup> * 7<sup>3</sup>",
            "c": "2<sup>5</sup> * 7",
            "d": "2<sup>7</sup> * 3<sup>2</sup> * 7<sup>2</sup>"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Determine the maximum area of a rectangle with perimeter 52.",
        "answer": "c",
        "choices": {
            "a": "25 sq. units",
            "b": "160 sq. units",
            "c": "169 sq. units",
            "d": "676 sq. units"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Solve for x in the given equation. <sqr>7-2x</sqr> = -7",
        "answer": "d",
        "choices": {
            "a": "-1",
            "b": "56",
            "c": "28",
            "d": "No solution"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Determine the point of intersection between the lines 5x + 7y = 34 and 3x -8y = -4",
        "answer": "c",
        "choices": {
            "a": "(11, -3)",
            "b": "(-3, 7)",
            "c": "(4, 2)",
            "d": "(2, 4)"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Determine the vertex of the quadratic function <i>f(x) = 3(x - 2)(x - 4).",
        "answer": "d",
        "choices": {
            "a": "(4, 0)",
            "b": "(2, 0)",
            "c": "(3, 8)",
            "d": "(3, -3)"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Simplify the expresion (3 + 5<sqr>2</sqr>)(4 - 2<sqr>2</sqr>)",
        "answer": "b",
        "choices": {
            "a": "10 - 12<sqr>2</sqr>",
            "b": "-8 +14<sqr>2</sqr>",
            "c": "9 + 10<sqr>2</sqr>",
            "d": "-5 + 4<sqr>4</sqr>"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "Given the set of scores {2, 5, 6, 2, 4, 3, 8, 7, 9, 2, 9}, sort the measures of central tendecies (mean, median, mode).",
        "answer": "c",
        "choices": {
            "a": "Mean < Mode < Median",
            "b": "Mode < Mean < Median",
            "c": "Mode < Median < Mean",
            "d": "Median < Mean < Mode"
        }
    },

    {
        "question": "The mean of a set of numbers is represented by the variable x. What is the new mean of the set after 5 is added to every number in the set?",
        "answer": "b",
        "choices": {
            "a": "5x",
            "b": "x+5",
            "c": "5x+5",
            "d": "x<sup>5</sup>"
        }
    }
]